Mattie Mae McKee papers, Inclusive: 1940-2018, undated, Bulk: 1968-1991, 2008-2016
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Mattie Mae McKee papers
Inclusive: 1940-2018, undated, Bulk: 1968-1991, 2008-2016
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
103
McKee, Mattie Mae, 1938 -
9 document boxes and 1 oversized box.
The Mattie Mae McKee papers consist of correspondence, photographs, and literary productions compiled by McKee while she worked as a congressional aide for five U.S. Representatives and Senators from 1968 to 1989. Most of the materials relate directly to her book published in 2014, In the Shadow of the Greats: From Texas' Square Roots to Capitol Hill's Inner Circle.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Mattie Mae McKee, the daughter of Sarah Taylor McKee and John Thomas McKee, was born in Sonora, Texas, on November 26, 1938. Her uncle, Basil Halbert Taylor, employed her throughout the summers of her high school years in the Law Office of Taylor & Murphy in San Antonio, instilling within McKee a love of the legal profession. After graduating from San Angelo High School in 1957, McKee earned her Associate’s degree in Business at San Angelo Junior College in 1959. She worked as a legal secretary for the firm of Kerr & Gayer where she earned her certification with the National Association of Legal Secretaries in 1966. At the time, McKee was one of twelve Certified Professional Legal Secretaries in Texas and the ninety-sixth to be certified in the nation.
Shortly thereafter, in March 1968, McKee entered the political arena as a congressional aide for Representative O.C. Fisher, a Democrat representing the 21st Congressional District of Texas. McKee worked for Representative Fisher until his decision to retire. In September 1974, McKee joined the staff of Representative W. R. Poage, a Democrat representing the 11th Congressional District of Texas. McKee remained as a member of Poage's staff until his decision to retire in December 1978. She then agreed to serve as the new Office Manager for Poage’s immediate successor, Democrat Marvin Leath. Under Leath, McKee faced the difficult task of establishing the office of a freshman Representative.
In July 1980, McKee left the House of Representatives behind and became the Executive Secretary for Senator John Tower of Texas, Chairman of the Senate Armed Services Committee. McKee held this position until January 1985 when Tower retired. McKee then accepted the Executive Assistant position for Senator John Warner of Virginia, remaining with his staff until April 1989 when McKee decided to leave Washington, D.C. and return to San Angelo.
After her lengthy career as a congressional aide, McKee earned a bachelor's degree in English and history at Angelo State University and worked briefly in the real estate field. She also pursued writing, co-authoring a two-volume history of her family, The Stories of the Taylors and Altizers: Passing It On, with her cousin in 2002. McKee later recounted her experiences in Washington, D.C. in her 2014 book, In the Shadow of the Greats: From Texas' Square Roots to Capitol Hill's Inner Circle.
Scope and Content
The chronology of the Mattie Mae McKee papers ranges from 1940 to 2018, although the bulk of the materials fall within the timeline of her career in Washington, D.C. (1968-1989). Mattie Mae McKee worked as congressional aide and staff member for three U.S. Representatives and two U.S. Senators: Representative O.C. Fisher (1968-1974), Representative W. R. Poage (1974-1978), Representative Marvin Leath (1979-1980), Senator John Tower (1980-1985), and Senator John Warner (1985-1989). All of these Congressmen represented McKee’s home state of Texas with the exception of Senator John Warner of Virginia.
The first five series follow the path of McKee’s career and are divided according to the appropriate Congressman. Similar types of materials are found throughout the collection, particularly correspondence, photographs, clippings, and programs. The donor also included research materials she gathered while compiling her book that was published in 2014, In the Shadow of the Greats. These documents have been placed in the relevant series, sometimes skewing the inclusive date ranges beyond the years McKee actually worked. The final series contains McKee’s personal materials relating to her book, research, and personal correspondence. Within each series, the folders are organized alphabetically by subject or material type. Series I. O.C. Fisher Years and Series IV. John Tower Years are the largest series in the collection.
Arrangement
The Mattie Mae McKee papers were initially housed in six record storage boxes. A detailed, folder-level inventory was completed just prior to the latest round of processing.
The original order of the collection has largely been maintained. The series are arranged chronologically according to the U.S. Representative or Senator for whom McKee worked. Within each series, folders are organized alphabetically by topic or material type.
A personal series was created to house materials produced after McKee's time in Washington, D.C., particularly documents pertaining to the writing of her book, In the Shadow of the Great s: From Texas' Square Roots to Capitol Hill's Inner Circle. Thus, the collection is currently arranged into six series: I. O.C. Fisher Years, II. W. R. Poage Years, III. Marvin Leath Years, IV. John Tower Years, V. John Warner Years, and VI. Personal.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 103. Acquired 2019-01-07
Related Resources
Items in related collections
William Robert "Bob" Poage Papers
Marvin Leath papers, Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
Ovie Clark "O.C." Fisher Papers, Inclusive: 1935-1978, Bulk: 1943-1974
Related references
Cochran, Mike. “Mattie McKee Detours Back Home After Life on Washington Fast Track.” Houston Post, November 25, 1990.
Cochran, Mike. “West Texan Looks Back on Days as Washington Insider.” Dallas Morning News, February 15, 1991.
Gatewood, Kandis. “Texas Asset in D.C.” San Angelo Standard-Times, July 19, 1981.
McKee, Mattie Mae. In the Shadow of the Greats: From Texas' Square Roots to Capitol Hill's Inner Circle. Ballinger, TX: Ballinger Printing & Graphics, 2014.
San Angelo Standard-Times, March 5, 1968.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Fisher, O.C. (Ovie Clark), 1903-1994.; Leath, James Marvin, 1931-2000.; McKee, Mattie Mae, 1938-; Poage, W. R. (William Robert), 1899-1987.; Tower, John G. (John Goodwin), 1925-1991.; Warner, John W., 1927-
Subjects (Organizations)
United States. Congress--Officials and employees.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Armed Services.; United States. Congress. House.; United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Armed Services.; United States. Congress. Senate.
Places
United States--Armed Forces.
Genres
Albums (Books); Business correspondence.; Certificates.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Ephemera.; Invitations.; Newsletters.; Obituaries.; Personal correspondence.; Photographs.; Programs (Publications).; Records (Documents)
- O. C. Fisher Years, 1940-2018, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  Series I. O.C. Fisher Years is one of the largest series in the collection and consists of clippings, photographs, correspondence, and other materials relating to Mattie McKee’s employment as a staff member for Representative O.C. Fisher. Fisher was a Democrat who represented the 21st Congressional District of Texas. McKee worked for Representative Fisher from March 1968 to September 1974. Materials relating to Fisher's membership on the House Armed Services Committee feature prominently in the series. The series is in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Photographic print; Postcards
  - 100th Anniversary of O C. Fisher Federal Building, Clippings, Correspondence, and Programs, 2011 August (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scouts Dinner Honoring O.C. Fisher, Clippings, Literary Productions, Photographs, and Programs, 1992, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Boy Scouts Dinner Honoring O.C. Fisher, Correspondence, 1992 February-July (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, General, 1968-2006, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Commissioning of U.S.S. L. Mendel Rivers, Address, Photographs, Press Releases, and Programs, 1975 February (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Secretaries Club, Program, 1970 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, General, 1974-2010, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Area Church of Christ Congressional Breakfasts, Correspondence, Notes, and Photograph, 1976, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dedication of O.C. Fisher Texas Historical Marker in Junction, Texas, Photographs and Remarks, 2018 November (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dewey Short, Helen Short Pauly, and Judge Robert S. Wiley, Correspondence and Research Materials, 1940-2008, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dolly Madison McKenna, Clipping and Promotional Materials, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Gem Meacham, Correspondence, Literary Productions, and Photographs (1 of 2), 1988-1992, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Gem Meacham, Correspondence, Literary Productions, and Photographs (2 of 2), 1988-1992, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Goodfellow Air Force Base, Correspondence, Program, and Speech, 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - John Robert Powers School, Finishing Course, Certificate, 1971 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - License Plate for Congress Staff, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Memoirs of Theo Alexander Regarding Fisher’s Race Against Representative Charles South, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Menu, House of Representatives Restaurant, Gerald Ford Presidential Inauguration, 1974-2018 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - National Register of Prominent Americans, Certificate, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Nine Governments and Flags of Bexar County, Certificate, 1969 November 26 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - O.C. Fisher, 90th Birthday Celebration, Clipping and Photographs, 1993 November (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - O.C. Fisher, Biographical Materials, 1971, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - O.C. Fisher, Newsletters from Retirement, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - O.C. Fisher, Obituaries, 1994 December (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - O.C. Fisher, Party Hosted by Mattie Mae McKee and Bob Daugherty, Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - O.C. Fisher Addition to Kimble County Library, Clippings, Correspondence, and Photographs, 1975-1989, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - O.C. Fisher Dam and Lake, Brochure and Clippings, 1975-2004 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Periodical, The Texas Association of Legal Secretaries Docket, 1967 March (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, General (1 of 10), 1963-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, General (2 of 10), 1963-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, General (3 of 10), 1963-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, General (4 of 10), 1963-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, General (5 of 10), 1963-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, General (6 of 10), 1963-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, General (7 of 10), 1963-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, General (8 of 10), 1963-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, General (9 of 10), 1963-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Photographs, General (10 of 10), 1963-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Postcards, 1973-1990, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Resume, Mattie McKee, circa 1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Richard Nixon’s Presidential Inauguration, Invitations, 1973 January 20 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sallie Griffis Helms, Obituary, 2013 March (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Santa Claus and Ebenezer Scrooge Race for Seat in House of Representatives, Clippings and Photographs, 1971, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Sidney Yudain, Clippings, Roll Call, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Sidney Yudain, Obituary, Photographs, and Remarks, 2013, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Sonora Fling Ding, Photographs (1 of 2), 1974-1978, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Sonora Fling Ding, Photographs (2 of 2), 1974-1978, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
- W. R. Poage Years, 1972-2009, undated; 2
  Series II. W. R. Poage Years is comprised of photographs, correspondence, programs, biographical materials, and other documents pertaining to Mattie McKee’s employment for U.S. Representative William Robert "Bob" Poage. Poage was a Democrat who represented the 11th Congressional District in Central Texas. McKee worked as his staff member from September 1974 to December 1978 at which time Representative Poage retired from public office. Overall, the materials in this series are in good condition.
  - Article, “W. R. Poage is Mr. Agriculture”, World of Agricultural Aviation, 1978 May (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, U.S.S. Beacon and U.S.S. Portland, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, General, 1975-1989, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, General, 1974-2004, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Groner Pitts Dinner and Roast, Brownwood Coliseum, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Helen Duprey Bullock, Biographical Materials, 1972-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Honorary Admissions Officer for West Point, Certificate, 1976 October (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Jimmy Carter’s Presidential Inauguration, Invitation and Program, 1977 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - O.C. Fisher Retirement Reception Hosted by W. R. Poage, Photographs (1 of 4), undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - O.C. Fisher Retirement Reception Hosted by W. R. Poage, Photographs (2 of 4), undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - O.C. Fisher Retirement Reception Hosted by W. R. Poage, Photographs (3 of 4), undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - O.C. Fisher Retirement Reception Hosted by W. R. Poage, Photographs (4 of 4), undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, General (1 of 5), 1977-1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, General (2 of 5), 1977-1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, General (3 of 5), 1977-1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, General (4 of 5), 1977-1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, General (5 of 5), 1977-1978, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Planting of Pecan Tree from Brownwood, Texas Near Capitol, Clippings, Correspondence, and Photographs, 1978-2009, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Postcards, 1981, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Statement of W. R. Poage Regarding Caucus Action, 1975 January 16 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Targeted Committee Chairmen, Biographical Materials and Photographs, 1976-2000, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Texas Breakfast Club, Correspondence and Photographs, 1976-2007 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Texas Breakfast Club, Remarks and Photographs, 1977 September (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Texas Day, Poetry, Photographs, and Program, 1976 May (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - W. R. Poage, Article on Service in Congress, 1978 November 2 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - W. R. Poage, Biographical Materials, 2009 April 30 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - W. R. Poage, Clipping on Retirement, 1977 September 25 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - W. R. Poage, Funeral Service Program, 1987 January 5 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - W. R. Poage, Tributes, 1978-2009 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - W. R. Poage and Baylor University Present His Oral Memoirs to Library of Congress, Correspondence and Photographs (1 of 2), 1985-2009 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - W. R. Poage and Baylor University Present His Oral Memoirs to Library of Congress, Correspondence and Photographs (2 of 2), 1985-2009 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - W. R. Poage Legislative Library Center Dedication, Brochure and Program, 1979 September 21 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Washington Views and News, Newsletters, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Marvin Leath Years, 1979-2000, undated; 3
  Series III. Marvin Leath Years is the smallest series in the collection. Mattie McKee worked as the Office Manager for Representative Marvin Leath from January 1979 to June 1980. Leath represented the 11th Congressional District in Central Texas, succeeding long-time Representative W. R. Poage. This series is comprised primarily of clippings and photographs from McKee's time in Leath's office and also includes a copy of Leath's obituary from 2000. The materials are in good condition.
  Photographic print
  - 11th Annual Real Texas Shindig, Advertisement, 1989 April 25 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bill Sims, Correspondence, 1980 June 17 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Charles Moore and Odessa [?], Photographs, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Clippings, 1989-1991, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Marvin Leath, Obituary, 2000 December (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Photographs (1 of 3), 1979-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photographs (2 of 3), 1979-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photographs (3 of 3), 1979-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- John Tower Years, 1977-2012, undated; 4
  Series IV. John Tower Years is the largest series in the collection. It is comprised of photographs, programs, correspondence, and other materials related to Mattie McKee’s employment as the Executive Secretary of Senator John Tower of Texas. McKee worked for Senator Tower from July 1980 until Tower’s retirement from the Senate in January 1985. Due to Tower’s service on the Senate Armed Services Committee, many of the materials in this series deal with the U.S. military (i.e. the commissioning of naval vessels, trips to West Point, Goodfellow Air Force Base, etc.). Tower’s nomination for Secretary of Defense under President George H. W. Bush, which was ultimately rejected by the Senate, is also prominently featured in the series. Overall, the materials are in good condition.
  - American Fighter Aces Association, Programs, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Article, “Texas Asset in D.C.”, San Angelo Standard-Times, 1981 July 19 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Baron Ewald Heinrich von Kleist, Biographical Materials, 1988-2008, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Black-Tie Dinner Hosted by Chief of Naval Operations James Watkins in Honor of John Tower, Photographs, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - British Embassy, Correspondence, Guides, and Photographs (1 of 2), 1982-1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - British Embassy, Correspondence, Guides, and Photographs (2 of 2), 1982-1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Change of Command Ceremony for Vice Admiral George E. R. Kinnear, Program, 1981 July 31 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Christening of the U.S.S. Alabama, Programs, 1984 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, General, 1984-2002, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Commissioning of the U.S.S. Carl Vinson, Program, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Commissioning of the U.S.S. Carl Vinson, Travel Itinerary, 1982 March 13 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Commissioning of the U.S.S. Corpus Christi, Binder, (1 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Commissioning of the U.S.S. Corpus Christi, Binder, (2 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Commissioning of the U.S.S. Corpus Christi, Clippings, Correspondence, Information Packets, and Photographs (1 of 4), 1975-2012, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Commissioning of the U.S.S. Corpus Christi, Clippings, Correspondence, Information Packets, and Photographs (2 of 4), 1975-2012, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Commissioning of the U.S.S. Corpus Christi, Clippings, Correspondence, Information Packets, and Photographs (3 of 4), 1975-2012, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Commissioning of the U.S.S. Corpus Christi, Clippings, Correspondence, Information Packets, and Photographs (4 of 4), 1975-2012, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Commissioning of the U.S.S. Corpus Christi, Periodical, The Dolphin, 1983 January 14 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Commissioning of the U.S.S. Houston, Program, 1982 September 25 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Confirmation Fight Over John Tower as Secretary of Defense, Clippings, 1988 December-1989 January (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Confirmation Fight Over John Tower as Secretary of Defense, Clippings, 1989 February 1-9 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Confirmation Fight Over John Tower as Secretary of Defense, Clippings, 1989 February 10-24 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Confirmation Fight Over John Tower as Secretary of Defense, Clippings, 1989 February 25-28 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Confirmation Fight Over John Tower as Secretary of Defense, Clippings, 1989 March 1-2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Confirmation Fight Over John Tower as Secretary of Defense, Clippings, 1989 March 3-7 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Confirmation Fight Over John Tower as Secretary of Defense, Clippings, 1989 March 8-29 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Staff Club, 47th Annual Dinner-Dance, Program, 1982 June 11 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, General (1 of 3), 1981-2012, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, General (2 of 3), 1981-2012, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, General (3 of 3), 1981-2012, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Personal Notes from the Tower Family, 1982-1992, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Deaths of John, Lilla, and Marian Tower, Clippings and Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Dedman College of Humanities and Sciences, Southern Methodist University, Newsletter, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Farnborough Air Show, Correspondence, Directories, and Itineraries (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Farnborough Air Show, Correspondence, Directories, and Itineraries (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Farnborough Air Show, Photographs, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - George H. W. Bush Administration, Inauguration Materials and Staff Directory, 1989 January, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Goodfellow Air Force Base, Correspondence, Photographs, and Programs (1 of 2), 1981-1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Goodfellow Air Force Base, Correspondence, Photographs, and Programs (2 of 2), 1981-1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Goodfellow Air Force Base and PAVE PAWS, Clippings, 1981, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - John and Marian Tower, Funeral Program, 1991 April 8 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Kappa Sigma Fraternity, Membership Materials, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - License Plate, Senate Staff, circa 1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Mighty Tower Art Players, Script, 1983 September 27 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Molly Pryor, Clippings, Correspondence, and Photograph, 1983-1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, General, 1981-1984, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Ronald Reagan, Speech at Alfalfa Club, 1986 January 25 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - San Angelo Symphony Orchestra, “A Gala Patriotic Salute to Goodfellow Air Force Base”, Program, 1984 April 28 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Texas Federation of Republican Women Award of Excellence, Certificate and Program, 1991 November 8-10 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Texas Independence Day Celebrations, Invitations and Speech Notes, 1999-2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Texas Independence Day Party in Washington, D.C., Clipping, Notes, and Photographs, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Texas Independence Day Party in Washington, D.C., Guestbook, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Tower Reunion Committee, Program and Roster, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Tower Staff Reunion Celebration, Photographs, 1982 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Trip to Houston for Tower’s Re-Election Campaign, Photographs, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)